<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/3.2.1" created="2011-11-13 16:22" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.1/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.1/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Blog of Shaun B.</title>
	<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws</link>
	<description>The thoughts of a person lost in code…</description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 16:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.1</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://blog.bentzen.ws</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://blog.bentzen.ws</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>Shaun</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>smb@bentzen.ws</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Shaun Bentzen]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Shaun]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Bentzen]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.2.1</generator>

	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=1</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2010 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://test.bentzen.ws/?p=1</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello all,

this is my first post and I'd like to say that I hope I am able to entertain you (the masses) enough that I'll have a good amount of readers and maybe if I feel like it, some meaningful discussions on code or whatever strikes my fancy.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>1</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2010-10-13 20:01:00</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2010-10-14 00:01:00</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>hello-world</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>OHAYO</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=10</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2010 02:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/2010/11/ohayo/</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello again,

In the past few weeks many a things have happened.
I have made it past the first round of the <a href="http://www.academynetriders.com/index.php">Cisco NetRiders</a> competition into the second round, which means that my teammate and I are one of the top ten in Ontario (in the competition). Along with that, school is going well, marks are stable, classes interesting and thought provoking and assignments are both a plenty and workable.

Work has been going well, the code is flowing in both appropriate and speedy fashion, sometimes when I don't want it to (gah, stop interrupting sleep) but all is well in that sense.

By the way, are there any good one column, dark word press layouts?

From the world of code,

Shaun B.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>10</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2010-11-08 21:06:55</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2010-11-09 02:06:55</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>ohayo</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Case studies and Stuff</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=14</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 01:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/2010/11/case-studies-and-stuff/</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello again,

As described in the title, I have begun case studies, or those massive labs at the end of a semester that encompass the entire curriculum. At the moment I only have one, though I expect to have at least 4 hooray Cisco switching and WAN accessing, and another hooray for Linux, and a whoop whoop for MS server admin. (you interpret if that was sarcasm or not).

Anyways, I've found an interesting tool that someone has shared with me, that I'd like to share with whomever is actually reading is blog. And that tool is <a href="http://splunk.com">Splunk</a> it's a log server, event tracker, performance monitor all racked into one product, put on anabolic steroids and then given crack. It can do windows event monitoring, cisco syslog, Linux syslog and performance monitoring and is an easy to install web service. Screenshot included<br/><br/><a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/20101116-085429.jpg"><img src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/20101116-085429.jpg" alt="" class="alignnone size-full" /></a>


And finally on a more personal note, all is well, and everything is coming together nicely, though I still have to work on that gosh darned landing page.

Shaun B.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>14</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2010-11-16 20:57:20</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2010-11-17 01:57:20</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>case-studies-and-stuff</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="labs"><![CDATA[labs]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="linux-admin"><![CDATA[Linux admin]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="network-tools"><![CDATA[network tools]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="personal"><![CDATA[personal]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="splunk"><![CDATA[splunk]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Hooray, Update</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=19</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 23:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/2010/12/hooray-update-2/</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone,

It has been a while, has it? I don't really know but either way, I'm writing.
I'm almost finished all of my classes for this semester, and that's good, just need to finish my psychology course and then free sailing from there.

So that means that I've finished another windows course and I also managed to finish my WAN and LAN Switching and Wireless course, which gives me a voucher for my CCNA exam, I think that saves about three hundred dollars?

Did I ever mention that I hate certificates? Cause man are those a pain in the arse for IIS and windows stuff, I mean sure, they give certificates out easy, they make issuing and revoking and enrollment easy, but revocation lists didn't want to work, I kept the bindings and everything and NOPE no revoked certs for you. Oh well.

I'm looking to learn how to play the cello, if someone would be so kind as to point to a good website (not that I can't find them myself) I'd just prefer if someone who's had good experience with a tutorial site would be so kind as to clue me in.

I'm hoping to maybe post some game reviews and tutorials and stuff when I get a new xbox and when I find something that I could post tutorials about.

Anyways, thanks for reading.

Shaun.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>19</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2010-12-13 18:50:23</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2010-12-13 23:50:23</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>hooray-update-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Long due update</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=26</link>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2011 20:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/2011/02/long-due-update/</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello everyone,

Been a while, and I actually have a lot to talk about! Well, onward with the show.

So, I've finished my fall semester with a 4.0 gpa, pretty fun stuff, I guess I could write my CCNA exam if I wanted to, I think I'll wait until the end of this semester though. Furthermore, Linux is becoming more and more interesting as my time in the class moves forwards, I'm learning about how to set up apache servers and bind9 among other things. I've already mentioned splunk, but the tool is just amazing, it's helped me figure out how to fix some of the more egregious errors on my server and has provided a good benchmark for what should be happening on a daily basis and what's completely out of ordinary. I would also like to mention that sharepoint is quite evil, there are so many things about it that make my head spin and just make me wish for something else. But, off of the bad stuff and onto the good. This semester has been quite entertaining, learning the advanced stuff in the Cisco curriculum, trying to make time to read some of my apple stuff and also trying to find a way to make my server log less.

On to other things, it was my birthday on February 3rd and I was pleasantly surprised to receive a tea set and an iTunes gift card, I bought an app called sparrow, it is amazing, it makes me revel in the minimalism of the design and wish that apple took some refreshers in UI design. I also started using dropbox, and I can't quite stop using it now. I don't have to bring a USB key around (unless there is no Internet in that area). I'm thinking of buying an SSH app for my iPod/iPad. I fully recommend dropbox to anyone who is sick of carrying USB keys around, you can just install it on your computers that you want files synced and drop the file into a folder, SHAZAM they're synced. If you want dropbox, go here <a href="http://db.tt/cxDXykg">To Dropbox</a>.

So, Netflix has been ruining some of my free time, I've been watching all of the anime's that I haven't had the time to find or drive to watch at the time. I highly recommend one called Mushi-shi. It's also given me the opportunity to watch all of the movies I haven't seen yet wanted to. If there is a movie you want to recommend go ahead and send one in.

So our Xbox 360 broke down a while ago, so we bought one over Christmas, no problems so far, got Alan wake and Forza Motorsport 3, haven't played either of them, but their on the list. Oh, by the way, I am completely psyched for the next elder scrolls game, i loved oblivion and this one only looks like a sizable improvement.

Finally, the issue of Usage based billing, I am completely against the imposition of limits upon my Internet use. I am not an expert on the issue, but I am knowledgeable on the underlying concepts network usage and consumption and find claims by the major cable companies and telcos to be outrageous and only for the benefit of increased profit and not the end user who doesn't use that much in terms of bandwidth, but to put it in perspective, your computer is always on, always transmitting data back and forth, and that would contribute towards your cap, even worse is when you do an upgrade on your computer at home, not everyone has a software update server, or windows update server to download and redistribute updates to their home computers, which means that you will download updates for every computer in your house, which means that there is a chance that the telecoms and cable companies are making money on keeping your computer and all of the software in it up to date. I would suggest going to <a href="http://stopthemeter.ca">StopTheMeter.ca</a> to learn more.

My landing page is on the way, I've been procrastinating too much on it and I'm going to get on it in the near future.

Thanks for listening,

Shaun.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>26</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-02-19 15:38:38</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-02-19 20:38:38</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>long-due-update</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="anime"><![CDATA[anime]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="apache"><![CDATA[apache]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="apps"><![CDATA[apps]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="bind9"><![CDATA[bind9]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="birthday"><![CDATA[birthday]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="cisco"><![CDATA[cisco]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="dropbox"><![CDATA[Dropbox]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="gripes"><![CDATA[gripes]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="linux"><![CDATA[Linux]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="netflix"><![CDATA[Netflix]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sparrow"><![CDATA[sparrow]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ubb"><![CDATA[ubb]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="videogames"><![CDATA[videogames]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="xbox"><![CDATA[xbox]]></category>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>April Update</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=28</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2011 15:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=28</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Man oh man has it been a while, oh well. So I've managed to finish another semester and man was this one hard, in the home stretch I was going into the lab almost every day doing case studies, labs to fill out my journal and labs just because I can (and with access to equipment like that, why not?) now that I'm all done, it's back to work and the competition that awaits me for May. I have a fun story from my programming, I was trying to include <a href="http://code.google.com/p/zxing/">ZXing</a> into my project and I was having issues with some random piece of C++ code, what I didn't realize until the end of the day was that my definition for != was the exact same as Apple's anonymous struct, which in turn meant that the code was using my definition over their code, which was weird, but oh well.

I've lately been back into StarCraft 2 and was wondering, does anyone out there have any weird or different build orders that could work with a little more refinement? I would like to know cause I'm always cool for new builds.

Anyways, short update, I'm sick, that's all.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>28</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-04-26 11:57:52</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-04-26 15:57:52</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>april-update</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>June Update</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=70</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2011 17:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=70</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Long time no post. Just wanted to get something out there and get an update as to what I'm doing. I've been playing a good amount of Starcraft 2 (is anyone else psyched for Heart of the Swarm?). I've also been working (the 1.2 update to iCambrian has been released) and we've got good download numbers and I've managed to make a good amount of fixes to some issues I've heard about. I'm now working on Version 2.0 and another app. I think I'm going to post some of my extensions onto Github and see what other development I can help with.

I've been trying to get some cello practice in, and it seems to be going well… haven't got to sheet music yet (still learning what sounds and feels right) and how to properly draw the bow.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>70</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-06-05 13:49:15</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-06-05 17:49:15</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>june-update</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Just an update</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=78</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2011 20:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=78</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hey this is just an update for the sake of updating. Lately I've wondered about OSX Lion and how someone would go about restoring their computer if they didn't have a backup of it, which brings me to think that it's would be really stupid to have to install snow leopard and then upgrade up to lion? sounds stupid but I've got faith in the solution <a href="http://osxdaily.com/2011/06/08/create-burn-bootable-mac-os-x-lion-install-disc/">here</a>.

I'm pretty psyched for IOS 5 and all the things it will hopefully bring developers better tools to make better applications for the iPhone/iPad. The big thing for me is the notification centre. I am so happy that they've heard the issues that people have had and decided to find a way to work on it.

Anywho… I've fallen back into stumbleupon (which is evil by the way) and have lost many hours to it like I did many years ago, I need to find something to distract myself from it, maybe minecraft will go well.

Anyways, that is all for now.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>78</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-06-19 16:37:56</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-06-19 20:37:56</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>just-an-update</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ios5"><![CDATA[IOS5]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="lion"><![CDATA[lion]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="minecraft"><![CDATA[minecraft]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="osx"><![CDATA[osx]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="stumbleupon"><![CDATA[stumbleupon]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Just a quick thought on 3.2</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=90</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 21:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=90</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Wow does it ever look nice… I especially like this new theme, it gives the whole site an up to date and clean look.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>90</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-07-07 17:04:58</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-07-07 21:04:58</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>just-a-quick-thought-on-3-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Revelation with GCD and NSXMLParser</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=93</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 00:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=93</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Recently while I was doing some work on an RSS parser for an iPhone application, I was having an issue with the parser not showing all the results, so I went and logged a bunch of stuff trying to figure out if it was just not returning enough stuff or not, and it turned out that it was, so that wasn't the problem, and every time I ran the code it would return a different amount of items, so I was looking through the code and decided to try something, which actually found me the correct answer, and that was what the difference between<code> dispatch_async() </code> and <code>dispatch_sync()</code>. So I'll go quickly through the difference.

Now, the allocation and other stuff isn't any different than usual
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://gist.github.com/1184518.js?file=GCDNSXML-Bad.m"></script>and right where the dispatch_async() is where the problem begins, as dispatch_async() returns immediately any results parsed in the fractions of seconds between the <code>[rssParser parse];</code> and the <code>tableview:(UITableView*)tableView cellForRowAtIndexPath:(NSIndexPath*)indexPath</code>are placed into your parsed results array, and any others after that are just orphaned into the bit bucket by not returning quickly enough. the fix to this is actually just one letter…<script type="text/javascript" src="https://gist.github.com/1184537.js?file=GCD+NSXML(GOOD).m"></script>

&nbsp;]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>93</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-07-10 20:30:37</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-07-11 00:30:37</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>revelation-with-gcd-and-nsxmlparser</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="development"><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="dev"><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="gcd"><![CDATA[GCD]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ios"><![CDATA[iOS]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="nsxmlparser"><![CDATA[NSXMLParser]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The weather… and other things</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=121</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 23:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=121</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Holy smokes is it hot, it feels like I'm dying of the heat, although realistically I'm not and it's much hotter elsewhere in the world it's still relatively hot for me. Otherwise,

[caption id="attachment_122" align="alignright" width="287" caption="30 Degrees"]<a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/Screen-shot-2011-07-17-at-7.00.40-PM.png"><img class="size-full wp-image-122 " title="The weather at 7" src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/Screen-shot-2011-07-17-at-7.00.40-PM.png" alt="The Weather" width="287" height="228" /></a>[/caption]

things are going well and work is going well too. I'm thinking of going on a training course some time in August to bump up on my certifications, only one more after that until the top. I think I'm going to move my landing page into WordPress so I have less sites and things to manage and maybe I can even make it look cool. I might even look into brining more content in, like StarCraft 2 replays ( I'm still horrible, maybe you can learn from that) or even a gallery or something, I don't know, I still have to figure out stuff, I may even do some more things like tutorials on Wednesday on some of the weird things that I've met in my 2 years of programming, which reminds me, I may decide to give a quick tutorial on how to have a separate delegate for UITableView so you don't have as many issues with bloating size, or keeping the view separate from the controller in the Data Source delegate.

I just started using <a href="http://mint.com">Mint.com</a>, it's really nice and is actually something that I may continue using throughout however long it is actually still alive (I hope it stays for a long while) and have just looked into a new app for the iPhone called <a href="http://www.situationistapp.com/">Situationalist</a>, you can either post one of the pre-made situations or make your own (i think) and anyone in the area can see that situation and respond to it, pretty cool if you ask me… there's too many good services coming out that I can't possibly use or even look at them all. If anyone actually reads this and has a good suggestion for a service for me to check out, just place it in a comment (keep in mind I'm in Canada and some services don't come here for some odd reason).

Anyways, I'm signing off.

See you all soon. (hopefully)]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>121</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-07-17 19:21:54</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-07-17 23:21:54</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-weather%e2%80%a6-and-other-things</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="canada"><![CDATA[Canada]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="development"><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="money-management"><![CDATA[Money Management]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sc2"><![CDATA[SC2]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="social-networking"><![CDATA[Social Networking]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="software"><![CDATA[Software]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="uitableviewcontroller"><![CDATA[UITableViewController]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="weather"><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="xcode"><![CDATA[XCode]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lion and other niceties</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=129</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 07:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=129</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello again, it's been a while and while I haven't got that Wednesday article I may still publish it if I can find the time to write it (I should probably put it into my task list). Well this weeks post is about Lion which I'm sure is very interesting to most people, I've got a few tips for that and the rest is about various things that have been happening in my life lately.

Firstly onto Lion, which is amazing, I was a part of the seeding program and have seen it develop from a pre-beta to what it is today and I must say it is a wondrous progression in the Mac OS line. The only beef I have with it is the scroll direction but I'll get used to it, and if I can't I can always change it back. My tip for lion is that if you find the library folder missing, run the following command <span style="color: #339966;">chflags -nohidden ~/Library</span>. I find the UI experience nicely polished and I don't mind the grey shift (not many people like this for some reason).

I have recently been invited to Google Plus which I still have to fill out and get more information into and add friends to it (it's like Facebook all over again) I will post more about it if I get past the initial hump of usage.

Finally in gaming news related to me, I've been playing team mono battles in Starcraft 2 and I have to mention how fun it is, it's almost taken me away from laddering, which won't happen, but I'm more prone to wandering during a season lock. I suggest you check it out, it's really fun, in a nutshell, you can only use one unit for offense and have to pick something that will support and complement your team.

Anyways I believe that is all for now.

Shaun]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>129</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-07-24 03:03:46</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-07-24 07:03:46</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>lion-and-other-niceties</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="beta"><![CDATA[beta]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="google-plus"><![CDATA[google plus]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="lion"><![CDATA[lion]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sc2"><![CDATA[SC2]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Silver, a new mouse and beyond…</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=130</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 03:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=130</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello all,

I noticed a search that came up for my blog and it was about not being able to find your Starcraft replays folder after updating to lion. The issue was that the replays folder was in the library (which hasn't disappeared), which I addressed in my last post (which has just been highlighted). Speaking of Starcraft, I managed to get out of bronze and into the silver league and I'm hoping to keep it up and not drop back down. my goal is get into the top eight in this season, which I have decided to get a new mouse because as nice as the magic mouse is… it's not good for gaming. The mouse that I got was the Razer Lachesis (with 5600dpi), it's a pretty nice mouse and can change the dpi settings on the fly with those two buttons at the scroll wheel.

[caption id="attachment_134" align="alignright" width="300" caption="New Mouse"]<a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/Photo-11-07-30-7-02-53-PM.jpeg"><img class="size-medium wp-image-134 " title="New Mouse" src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/07/Photo-11-07-30-7-02-53-PM-300x225.jpg" alt="Razer Lachesis with Orange tint" width="300" height="225" /></a>[/caption]

Onto other business… work is going very well, I've managed to get some cool things going conceptually in the application I'm developing and I'm going on training course during August. This week I'm definitely going to put that UITableView tutorial up (I've put it off too long)

On personal matters, This weekend I'm helping build shed doors at home (cause the person who made them before was a macguyver) and hopefully will get time to practice with my cello and play some starcraft on this long weekend.

I believe that's good enough for now, I may post my full review/thoughts of lion some time soon.

Thanks for reading!]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>130</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-07-30 23:11:06</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-07-31 03:11:06</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>silver-a-new-mouse-and-beyond%e2%80%a6</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="construction"><![CDATA[Construction]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="development"><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hidden-folder"><![CDATA[Hidden Folder]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="lachesis"><![CDATA[Lachesis]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="lion"><![CDATA[lion]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="macguyver"><![CDATA[Macguyver]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mice"><![CDATA[Mice]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="razer"><![CDATA[Razer]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="shed"><![CDATA[Shed]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="starcraft"><![CDATA[Starcraft]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Minecraft and Stuff</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=139</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 01:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=139</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[I'd like to quickly start this off by briefly saying that mine craft is addictive, not as addictive as starcraft, however it is addictive none the less. I started off the game and knew nothing, so I built the customary wooden pickaxe and started mining things and found my self into a dungeon,  which ended in a similar fashion as my endeavour in Runescape, dying in a horrific manner and losing all of my items, however, unlike Runescape, I had a goal in mind I want to build a beautiful house so I continue on… more will come up when the house is done (pictures, videos).

Otherwise, not much new in my life, just relaxing and enjoying the summer, can't wait for school to start as it looks like I have a good semester (everything in the middle) and this will be my last year in college (after high school, you never know where life will take you afterwards). It's gotten so cool around here, it's dropped from about thirty to about twenty-five. I apologize for the lack of posting (if anyone actually reads this) and I may or may not post something about UITableView if I have the time for it. I am looking for cheap repository hosting and I've seen beanstalk and Github and I like them and I wonder if there are any that are less expensive or have better features, if not I'll just end up self hosting it (no matter how potentially unstable the internet is).

That's all for now]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>139</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-08-14 21:27:14</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-08-15 01:27:14</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>minecraft-and-stuff</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="beanstalk"><![CDATA[Beanstalk]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="code-hosting"><![CDATA[Code Hosting]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="git"><![CDATA[Git]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="github"><![CDATA[Github]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="minecraft"><![CDATA[minecraft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="runescape"><![CDATA[Runescape]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Journeying off...</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=149</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2011 02:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=149</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Well, I'm starting my vacation this weekend and first stop is Toronto, visiting family, to which i will then go to Ottawa and visit friends (and play video games) not much else has been happening personally, well, other than moving some of my code off my personal server to github (which I absolutely love) because git allows me to commit without having to be connected to the Internet to reach the repository, which is a huge plus. Any who, so far it's been raining for about an two hours on this drive down, probably going to be raining the whole way down and probably there too. If anyone reads this, could you tell me where to get a fennec fox in northern Ontario, if you even can get one north of Toronto.

Update: I got completely soaked in the Scarborough town centre station, not too much protection from the rain.


At work things are shaping up pretty well for the next release of the application and oh boy does it look like it will be a good release, new graphics, better UI structure, more features and less bugs (I hope).

I still have more decorating to do in minecraft before I show the creation off, however, it's getting better than it was a week ago, I need to go exploring in my little world some more. I may post some Starcraft stuff if I feel like it. I also hope to at least stay in silver league for this season (above 25) and hopefully move up to gold league.

Thanks for reading.<br /><br /><a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/20110821-102330.jpg"><img src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/20110821-102330.jpg" alt="20110821-102330.jpg" class="alignnone size-full" /></a>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>149</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-08-21 22:22:24</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-08-22 02:22:24</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>journeying-off</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Good Vacation</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=154</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2011 03:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=154</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Well… my vacation is essentially over… so back to work it will be… I've been playing a good amount of video games and just generally relaxing for the past week. there have been some videos I've found on the internet that have sparked my interest even further for minecraft and I'm getting more stuff for the house and I'm hopefully going to post something about it some time soon. in other personal news… I left my hat on the greyhound bus and it's gone. I also have a picture to show… it's of some graffiti that I found in an underpass in the Nepean area in Ottawa.<a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/IMG_0003.jpg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-155" title="U Mad Superbro?" src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/08/IMG_0003.jpg" alt="" width="960" height="720" /></a>

More news… school is starting soon and that means potentially less updates (but since no one even reads this it's not like it matters) and more learning… and graduation. this will be one of my last semesters before graduation and getting my diploma and then entering the world of work. On the topic of school, I am so pleased that I can find my books online through e-book stores like peach pit and affiliates and others like O'Reilly and Amazon.

i genuinely hope that my bus tomorrow has internet on it… cause if it does that will be ample time to post that UITableView post I've been wanting to make for a while.

&nbsp;

Anyways… that's all for now.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>154</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-08-27 23:23:29</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-08-28 03:23:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>good-vacation</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="diploma"><![CDATA[diploma]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="e-books"><![CDATA[e-books]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="hat"><![CDATA[Hat]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="minecraft"><![CDATA[minecraft]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ottawa"><![CDATA[Ottawa]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="school"><![CDATA[school]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="uitableview"><![CDATA[UITableView]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="vacation"><![CDATA[Vacation]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>I saw a bat today…</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=163</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2011 23:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=163</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[I saw a bat today, I was on the fourth floor at the college, sitting on a bench and out of the blue I saw this tiny black thing crawling across the wall, so I looked at it and took some pictures. I find it cute.<a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Photo-11-09-08-8-32-07-AM-e1315523567914.jpeg"><img class="alignright size-full wp-image-164" title="Photo 11-09-08 8 32 07 AM" src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Photo-11-09-08-8-32-07-AM-e1315523567914.jpeg" alt="" width="720" height="960" /></a>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>163</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-09-08 19:13:54</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-09-08 23:13:54</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>i-saw-a-bat-today%e2%80%a6</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Second Week in…</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=167</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=167</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[So it's the second week into school and I'm already feeling tired. Although it is nice to get back into the feel of things. The classes I have this year are really interesting and hopefully I'll be able to pull a lot from them. In the mean time I've fiddled around with Windows 8 and Mac OS X Lion Server (I would eventually like to move my Snow Leopard server to Lion). Speaking of servers and things related to them, VMWare came out with their fourth revision of Fusion, which I find quite nice as it allows lion and windows 8 virtualization along with cleaning up the user interface and making some adjustments to performance and the likes, overall I'd give it a 5 out of 5.

[caption id="attachment_170" align="alignright" width="584" caption="The weather in Windows 8"]<a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Screen-Shot-2011-09-17-at-7.30.05-PM.png"><img class="size-large wp-image-170" title="Screen Shot 2011-09-17 at 7.30.05 PM" src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Screen-Shot-2011-09-17-at-7.30.05-PM-1024x821.png" alt="" width="584" height="468" /></a>[/caption]

Things have been going well in my life… I'm still relatively high in my silver league (hoping to get to gold) and I'm still thoroughly enjoying minecraft (1.8 is awesome). I'm slowly getting better with the cello and will definitely buy one when my rental is up. Another thing I'm slowly getting into is more open source work that will hopefully get me back into wanting to program for the fun of it, mostly I'm looking to get back into ruby/ruby on rails. I may have mentioned it before… but I absolutely love github. It is just amazing for source code management along with issue management, group access to code and wikis/webpages for the code.

Some of the new things I've tried lately is the iWork Suite for the iPad, and I must say it works very well… and the webdav saving feature is just cool, I could set it up on my dropbox and have pseudo-native dropbox support.

If I don't get any real comments within the next while I'm just going to disable it completely.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>167</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-09-17 20:20:58</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-09-18 00:20:58</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>second-week-in%e2%80%a6</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Ahh Fall</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=183</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2011 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=183</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Well… fall has arrived and, I must say I'm not to disappointed that summer has left us for this year. the weather isn't at all that unbearable and has only on occasion drifted to around 2°c in the mornings. even the leaves are changing now, and wow do they ever look pretty. I took the picture below just outside the house. I have recently bought a <a href="http://scottevest.com">Scottevest</a> it hasn't arrived yet but hopefully that will be soon and I will get to try it out and stay warm wherever (luckily I bought the lightweight and not the travel vest, my father says its too warm during the summer/fall). I'm still around 16th in my SC2 league (although I'm not playing much because of school and work) but hopefully I'll move up to gold for the end of this season or the beginning of next one. I find it sad that the only comments that I would get throughout the time I had comments opened up was spam, so I closed them last time and now I officially don't care whether people read or not. I'm probably going to put this on stumble upon but that might not do much as I don't have much content. In minecraft news, I haven't had much time to create much, just been blowing stuff up (infinite TNT is fun) and hopefully I'll have something cool to show to people when its finished, I may even just show it off for the fun of it as an unfinished project.<a href="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Photo-11-09-24-5-17-23-PM.jpg"><img class="alignright size-large wp-image-185" title="Fall Now" src="http://blog.bentzen.ws/wp-content/uploads/2011/09/Photo-11-09-24-5-17-23-PM-1024x764.jpg" alt="" width="584" height="435" /></a>

Anyways… good things are happening with work, I've managed to submit the app update that I've been working on and holy smokes do I hate regressions, but they all got fixed so that's good. hopefully it will be in the store by the middle of this week (it's waiting for review) and then I can continue work on one of the other plethora of projects I have simmering. I actually can't mention how much I love Github, it's solved so many things just by existing, want to see a branch graph and when they've merged together, DONE! do you want to see the impact you've had on the code, there's a graph for it, how about when people are committing/pushing to get an exact time of when people do most of their work? there's a graph for that.

In other news, I'm planning on some more development work on my landing page to make it look better, hopefully that's a task I can achieve with all the school and work going on.

I'm going to add more sites I'm on to the top bar and re-open comments for this week.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>183</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-09-25 12:56:48</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-09-25 16:56:48</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>ahh-fall</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="development"><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="dev"><![CDATA[Development]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="fall"><![CDATA[Fall]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="github"><![CDATA[Github]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="graphs"><![CDATA[Graphs]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="minecraft"><![CDATA[minecraft]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="quality-assurance-testing"><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Testing]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sc2"><![CDATA[SC2]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Another week gone by.</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=197</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2011 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=197</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Well there goes the week. It was a good week too. I was able to play video games, sent out an update for the app that I have and still am working on since the summer, prepare an update for another application for review and working on a cool new project. Things are slowing down a bit from the haze of activity that was the first month of coming back to school and I'm actually quite happy about it, now I have more video game time.

School has been good, getting some cool stuff done with my AD administration class (recently got into FSMO roles) and I'm hoping to test this stuff on my personal equipment when I have the time for it. Have I ever mentioned how much I love google's collaboration suite? I've got a couple of projects for two classes and with google docs and stuff we can all work on it all at the same time to get the job done. Even better about it is we can chat while working on the document to get the true collaboration experience.

Hopefully I'll get more time on the SC2 ladder when things die down a bit more, as I've floated in the teens in my league, hopefully I'll get to gold some time soon but, if I don't it will not that big of an issue because I'm sure that within a couple of games of a league reset I'll be there anyways.

Something you should look out for when you're looking for cool things to buy is the <a href="http://scottevest.com">Scottevest</a> I bought one and it's just great, it's got pockets, warmth and a bit of style too. I may post pictures of myself wearing it but that's an unknown.

It's been a pretty quiet sunday leading into hopefully a good busy (not too busy) week.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>197</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-10-02 15:25:55</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-10-02 19:25:55</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>another-week-gone-by</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="ad"><![CDATA[AD]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="collaboration"><![CDATA[Collaboration]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="fsmo"><![CDATA[FSMO]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sc2"><![CDATA[SC2]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="school"><![CDATA[school]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="scottevest"><![CDATA[scottevest]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sunday"><![CDATA[sunday]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Thanksgiving Update</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=202</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2011 17:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=202</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello Everyone,

Things are going well, I've managed to do one thing on my personal website (added a github banner to it) and I'm planning to do some more to it, cleaning up the way the stuff at the bottom looks, maybe putting more relevant stuff in there. It's been quite warm here for the past couple of days, around the 30°c mark, and that's saying something for October. The workload for school seems to be tapering off, which is nice as it's giving me more free time to do my own personal things (like post here) and play video games. Maybe I'll be able to post something cool soon.

I'm pretty excited for IOS5, which is set to release on the 12th of this month, I've been beta testing/developing with it since it was first introduced in the betas and I'm pleased with how it's turned out, hopefully the rollout won't be as painful on me as it was for IOS4 (when people were tweeting like rabid birds) and hopefully it won't eat my devices and force me to restart all of them from scratch. iCloud looks interesting, I can't quite say I'll buy more into it past the initial 5 free gigabytes. I've tested that as well and it looks quite nice too, refined UI for the services that are web offered and seamless integration like mobile me should have been.

So things have gone well in Starcraft for me, I'm still in silver league, but I'm not really playing too many games and hopefully I'll get to gold for next season (and stay there) which happens to start around the 24th of this month, with the league lock starting either today or tomorrow. I really hope I am getting better, but I really don't know as it's always hard to assess yourself.

Thanks for reading!]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>202</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-10-10 13:15:56</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-10-10 17:15:56</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>thanksgiving-update</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Getting busy again.</title>
		<link>http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=208</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2011 18:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Shaun</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://blog.bentzen.ws/?p=208</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[Man oh man are things getting busy again, I've got some tests, assignments and other stuff to do. Work is going well and I hope to do some fun stuff with IOS5 and its new features. Starcraft 2 is going pretty well, The leagues are locked and I've stayed in the same relative position for this whole season and hopefully I'll be able to get to gold for the next season. I'm also watching MLG at the moment and it's actually so scintillating that I'm drawn in with a want to play.

That's all I can post about at the moment as there's not really anything new going on this week.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>208</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2011-10-16 14:25:50</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2011-10-16 18:25:50</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>getting-busy-again</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="mlg"><![CDATA[MLG]]></category>
		<category domain="category" nicename="me"><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="sc2"><![CDATA[SC2]]></category>
		<category domain="post_tag" nicename="school"><![CDATA[school]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
